原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译     累
校对     累
时间轴     想念Gallifrey的Wholock    累
后期     累
总监     累
骑马去东边的草场看看  凯斯
Ride those east pastures, Kayce.
这么大雨  看看有没有苜蓿冒出来
With all this rain, see if any of that clover came up.
嗯  应该很容易发现
Yeah. It'll be easy to spot.
你今晚回来吗
You gonna be back by tonight?
放弃一件事很快的  孩子
Doesn't... Doesn't take long to quit something, son.
我中午就回来
I'll be back by noon.
走吧
Let's go.
来  车里穿吧
Here. You'll dress in the car.
泰特  泰特  看着我
Tate. Tate. Look at me.
泰特  泰特  行了  没事  没事的
Tate, Tate, stop. It's okay, it's okay.
别闹了
Stop.
别说了
Don't say it.
不用说
I don't have to.
我没什么好话可以说了
I can't say it any better than that.
没事的
It's okay.
继续睡吧  儿子  好吗
Just... Just go back to sleep, son, okay?
黄石
第三季  第一集
照我说的复述就行  明白吗
Exactly as I told you to say it, understood?
明白  相信我
Understood. Trust me.
相信我
Trust me?
他会走进来
He's gonna walk in here--
不行
Okay, no.
你好  约翰
Hello, John.
莉奈儿
Lynelle.
我不知道从何说起
I, uh... I don't know where to start.
我知道
I know where to start.
我们有证据表明贝克兄弟用飞机
We had evidence that the Becks used aircraft
在埃米格兰南边89号公路旁边毒牛
to poison cattle along the highway 89 corridor south of Emigrant.
根据此信息发出逮捕令
Upon serving a warrant based on that information,
我们发现了绑架的证据
we discovered additional evidence of a kidnapping--
这些我们都知道  杰米
We know all this, Jamie.
畜牧协会探员有法律义务打击任何犯罪行为
Livestock agents are bound by law to intervene in any active crime.
职责高于管辖范围
That duty supersedes jurisdictional boundaries.
你要反抗吗  约翰
You gonna fight this, John?
我们说错了吗
Are we wrong?
你说的没错  但这并不会改变事情的角度
You're not wrong. But it doesn't alter the lens.
不会改变观察的途径和方式
It doesn't change the way it looks and how it looks--
这才是最重要的  约翰
Is all that matters anymore, John.
六个人死了
Six people died.
门关上了  约翰
The door is closed, John.
实话实说吧
Let's just be honest.
到时候毯子一拉开
When the blanket gets pulled back on this thing,
全国人民都知道
and the nation knows that the family member
被绑架的是你的
that was kidnapped was yours...
这就不像在执法
This stops looking like law enforcement
-而是  -世仇
- and starts looking like... - It looks like a feud.
看起来像是公报私仇
It looks like a gross misuse of power.
我们在这里想破脑袋
We have been sitting here banging our heads against a wall,
也没有想到解决办法
and we don't have a solution.
我有个办法  莉奈儿
I have a solution, Lynelle.
把毯子留在原处
You leave the blanket right where it is.
我辞去牲畜委员会委员
I'll resign as Livestock Commissioner
并为我的探员的过激行为负全责
and accept full responsibility for my agents' overreach.
你就不用盯着了
And you, you stop looking.
放手吧
You let it go.
你就说是民兵和人口走私
You talk about militias and human smuggling
功劳都归你
and you take the credit.
别把我和我的家人扯进来
And you leave me and my family out of it.
我觉得没问题
That cleans things up on my end.
这是州政府的事  就这么定了
This is a state issue and that's where I want it to stay.
你们不会插手了吗
And this keeps it a state issue?
是的  我得到了我想要的
It gives me what I need, yes.
很好
Great.
你想过接替的人吗
Have you thought about your replacement?
下周告诉你
Give me till next week.
谢谢你  约翰
Thank you, John.
我不会忘记的
I won't forget this.
我不会让你忘记的
I won't let you.
那肯定
I'm sure you won't.
牲畜委员会委员约翰·达顿和州长
There was a closed door meeting with the Governor,
检察长  联邦官员
the Attorney General, Federal Officials,
进行了一次秘密会议
and Livestock Commissioner John Dutton.
达顿办公室因为在多次枪战中使用暴力
Now, Dutton's office is under intense scrutiny
正在接受严格审查
for its use of force in multiple gun battles
你觉得他会有什么下场
How do you think this is gonna work out for him?
取决于他是否像我想的那么聪明
Depends, on whether he's as smart as I think he is.
我在外面观察过他
I watched him. In a field.
他有尊严  大多数人都没有
He had honor when most wouldn't.
你什么意思
What are you saying?
也许他不是我们想象中的敌人
I'm saying, maybe he's not the enemy we think he is.
当两个男人想要一样东西时
When there's one thing that two men want,
他们要么分享  要么是敌人
they can either share it or be enemies.
你是建议我们分享吗
Are you suggesting we share it?
建议不是我的工作  主席
Suggesting things isn't my job, Chairman.
而是你的工作
That's yours.
这边看起来还行
This side looks good.
这边也是
This side too.
把牛赶出去的感觉好吗
You feel good turning cattle back out?
上场雨下完  应该要长苜蓿的
It should have clovered up this last rain.
我觉得我们应该等到七月
I think we ought to wait until July.
我们没有干草了
We're running out of hay.
喂一夏天牛可不是谋生之道
Feeding cattle all summer is no way to make a living.
我靠  我们就跟以前一样
Shit, we'll just do it like the old days:
弄个流动炊事车
grab a chuck wagon, bring it out here
照顾它们一夏天
and we'll babysit 'em all summer long.
这主意其实还行
It's not the worst idea.
搞什么鬼
The fuck?
他们是谁
Who the fuck are they?
你们迷路了吗
Y'all lost?
有可能
It's a possibility.
这是天堂谷运动俱乐部吗
Is this part of the Paradise Valley Sporting Club?
在围栏的另一边
Wrong side of that fence.
我说吧
I told you.
你们都住在运动俱乐部吗
You all staying at the Sporting Club?
他们是股东
They own it.
他们是谁
Who are they?
普罗维登斯酒店管理公司
Providence Hospitality management.
我叫埃利斯·斯蒂尔
I'm Ellis Steele.
我的律所代表市场股票
My firm is representing Market Equities.
我们不懂这玩意
We don't know what that is.
他们管理度假村
They manage resort properties.
我们为他们的利益着想
We watch out for their interests.
这是你的土地吗
This your land?
不可思议
Incredible.
我还不知道你的名字呢
I didn't catch your name?
因为我没说
That's cause I didn't offer it.
也是
Fair enough.
我们马上就走
We'll get out of your way.
我能理解你的谨慎
You know, I can understand you being wary,
一群城里人在你的土地上瞎晃
bunch of city folks wandering in your field.
我道歉
I apologize.
来度假村吃晚饭吧  我们请客
Why don't you come by the resort and have dinner, on us?
毕竟  你们会成为邻居
After all, you're going to be neighbors,
以和为贵嘛
it's best if we all get along.
这边  伙计们
We're going this way, folks.
红色标注的地产是我们买的
The properties highlighted in red are the ones we've purchased.
多少英亩
How much acreage total?
一万七千多一点
A little over 17,000.
我靠
Damn.
厉害啊  贝丝
Good job, Beth.
不然你也不会雇我
It's what you pay me to do.
有商业用地吗
Any of it commercially zoned?
临近高速的地产大多是多功能的
Most of the highway frontage is multi-use.
边角的地产是商用的
But the corner properties, they're commercial.
怎么了  你在想什么
Why, what you thinking?
我希望你可以暂缓保护地役权
I want you to hold off on the conservation easements.
那部分收入可以抵消我们的税收负担
That income offsets our tax liability.
我知道  但以后可能会有更多收入
I know, but there could be bigger income on the horizon.
市场股票买了詹金斯的地
Market Equities bought Jenkins' place.
雇了一个酒店管理团队来监督
Hired a hotel management group to oversee it.
动作很快啊
That was fast.
詹金斯别无选择
The estate didn't have a choice.
他每月损失六位数呢
He was losing six figures a month.
银行本来都要让他抵押了
Bank was going to call the note.
现在是谁在管理这处地产
So, who is running the property now?
普罗维登斯
Providence.
那可是家大公司
That's a big company.
当你的目标是扩张时  就会把他们牵扯进来
It's the one you bring in when your goal is expansion.
你的扩张范围并不仅限于赌场和高尔夫球场
And your expansion is bigger than casinos and golf courses.
你听说他们的计划了吗
You heard any rumors about their plans?
可能和他们在奥斯汀和斯科茨代尔的计划一样
Probably the same as their plans in Austin and Scottsdale.
贝丝  继续买入
Beth, keep buying.
只要能买  就尽管买
Buy every fucking thing you can get your hands on.
好的
Will do.
旧马厩怎么了
What's wrong with the old barn?
那里离农场这半边有七英里呢
It's seven miles from this half of the ranch.
罗伊德  那个
Hey, Lloyd, what, uh...
那个老笑话是什么来着
What was that old joke about the two fat chicks
两个肥妞和手推车的那个
and the wheelbarrows?
那不是笑话  杰克
That wasn't a joke, Jake.
那是你在库珀家的糗事
That was you at the Cooper branding.
你们想听个笑话吗
You guys wanna hear a joke?
不想
No.
听着
All right, check it out.
有个得州石油大亨
There's this big Texas oil guy, right?
走进边境的一家酒吧
Goes into this bar down at the border,
坐在牧人旁边说
sits next to this vaquero and says,
"哥们  你是牧场主吗"
"Hey, man, you a rancher?"
牧人说"嗯  我在河边有50英亩地"
Vaquero says, "Yeah, I got fifty acres down by the river."
得州石油大亨说"在我的农场
Big Texas oil guy says, "Oh? Oh, on my ranch,
我早上坐上我的卡车
I can get in my truck in the morning,
日落前都到不了大门"
and I still don't reach the front gate by sunset."
牧人坐了一会儿  点头说
Vaquero sits for a second, nods, and says,
"是啊  伙计  我以前也有一辆那样的卡车"
"Yeah, man. Yeah, I used to have a truck like that too."
我
I...
他在吹嘘他的牧场有多大
He was bragging about the size of his ranch,
-牧人以为  -我差点就笑了
- and the vaquero... - That was almost funny.
我想到一个
All right, I got one.
有个人去看医生
Y'all hear about the guy that goes to see a doctor,
医生说"很遗憾告诉你
and the doctor says, "Sorry to be the one to tell you this,
但你从头到脚都有癌症
But you got cancer head to toe.
只剩一周可活了"
Only have one week to live."
他说"一周  那可不够啊
Man says, "A week?! Well, that's not enough time!
医生  你得做点什么
Doc, you gotta do something.
一周可不够"
I need more than a week!"
医生想了想  坐下说
And the Doc thinks, he sits down and he says,
"你这样吧
"I'll tell you what to do:
你去找个养两只狗的绕桶赛女孩
You go find yourself a barrel racer girl
然后把她给娶了"
with two little dogs, and you marry her."
那个人说"这样就能活得更久吗"
And the man says, "That's gonna make me live longer?"
医生说"不是
And the Doc says, "No.
但你这周肯定度日如年"
But it'll make that week feel like a fucking eternity."
我觉得我的更好笑
I don't know. I think mine was better.
吉米  等你长大了
Jimmy, when you're all growed up,
谈个恋爱
and you've actually dated a woman,
你就会觉得好笑了
you'll think it's hilarious.
好了  我们去大马厩吧
That's it. Let's go up to the big barn.
你这边完事了  走吧
You're done. Let's go.
罗伊德  把骡子赶出去
Lloyd, let's get them mules out of the field.
我们去把流动炊事车清理一下
Let's clean up that chuck wagon.
我们今年夏天要弄尖刺营地  明白吗
We're running a spike camp this summer, understand?
伊森  走吧
Ethan, come on.
等等  尖刺营地是什么
Wait, what's a spike camp?
38块
It's 38 even.
捐点钱吗
Care to donate to the jar fund?
请帮助支付医药费
谢谢
当然
Sure.
不用了
Oh, I'm good.
你应该开个"资助我"的页面
You know, you should start a "GoFundMe" Page.
那是什么
What's that?
是
It's, um...
全世界都可以捐赠的泡菜罐
It's a pickle jar the whole world can reach.
你儿子吗
Your boy?
你都搞捐赠了  他还打你
Dealing with this and he still does that to you?
你也被人打了
Someone's doing it to you, too.
以后不会了
Not anymore they're not.
怎么
How...
你怎么做到的
How did you make him stop?
我男友把他的头按进墙里
My boyfriend put his head through a wall,
我用一个八磅重的烟灰缸砸了他的头
then I smashed his skull with an eight pound ashtray.
新男友
New boyfriend.
大烟灰缸
Big-ass ashtray.
这只是个建议
It's just a thought...
普罗维登斯酒店管理公司怎么了
What's Providence Hospitality?
他们是个麻烦
It's a problem.
多麻烦
How big?
他们不会继续惹麻烦了
They don't get any bigger.
别告诉老爸  可以
Listen, don't tell Dad. Okay?
我挂了  有个混蛋站在我们的河里
I gotta go, some asshole's standing in our river.
你好啊
How ya doing?
你这是非法入侵
You're trespassing!
非法入侵
Trespassing!
什么
What?
滚出我们的河
Get out of our fucking river.
不行  那是非法入侵
I can't That would be trespassing.
这傻逼
This fucking guy...
我发现这个山谷里的女人越来越时髦了
I see the women in this valley have gotten a lot more fashionable.
是吗
Yeah?
我发现齐本德尔改变了假牙政策
I see Chippendale's changed their policy on capped teeth.
什么
What's that?
骂你呢
It's an insult.
算了
Never mind.
骂人也得让给人听懂啊
Only an insult if I understand it.
其实不用
Yeah, that's not true.
但是这话下次再说吧
But that's a conversation for another time.
其实根本没有下次了
That we'll never have.
河的两岸都是私人领地
Both sides of the river are private property.
我知道  所以我出不去啊
I know. That's why I can't get out.
你怎么进来的
Well, how did you get in?
上游有个地方是我家的
My family owns a place upriver.
十字溪农场  你知道吗
Cross Creek Ranch. You know it?
嗯  可是那在上游五英里啊
Yeah, that's five miles upstream.
还好我精力旺盛
I was blessed with stamina.
我深表怀疑
I highly doubt it.
我打高尔夫  一天能打36个洞
When I played golf, I'd do 36 holes in a day.
我更喜欢这样
I like this much better.
这很像高尔夫  不过把球换成了鱼
It's just like golf, but with fish.
一起吃个晚饭吗
You have any interest in dinner?
不用了
No.
我不是特指今晚
I meant in general.
不用  我以快乐为生
No. I dine on my joy for life.
离我们的地盘远点  好吗
Just stay off our fucking land, okay?
遵命  长官
Yes, ma'am.
我会离你的地盘远点
I'll stay off your fucking land.
我保证
I promise.
谢谢你来找我聊天
Thanks for the talk!
你是我今天遇到的最有趣的事
You're the most interesting thing that's happened to me today.
你还是好好琢磨一下吧
You should analyze that.
怎么样
How'd it go?
如我所料
Like I expected.
这对他们来说是笔好交易
It's a good trade for them.
他们很高兴
They were happy to make it.
你呢  你高兴吗
How bout you? You happy?
我压根就不想当官  贝丝
I never wanted that office, Beth.
我只是  喜欢掌控大局
I just... wanted the control.
现在控制权依然在我手里
I still have that.
这好像有点难以信服
This might be a tougher sell.
这不是还好有你嘛
Well, lucky I got you to sell it for me.
草场怎么样
How are the fields?
很绿
They're green.
没有苜蓿吗
No clover?
我没看到  不过草长得很高
None that I could see. Grass is tall, though.
我在想我们应该建个营地
I was thinking we should run a camp up there
继续盯着
and keep an eye on 'em.
天堂谷那边有情况
Oh, and there's something going down at Paradise Valley.
有一堆西装革履的人
There's a bunch of suits
在那里闲逛
wandering around up there when we got up there.
西装
Suits?
是啊  我正要说呢
Yeah, I was gonna get to that.
一次解决一个问题
Well, one problem at a time.
我要任命一个新人接替我的职位
I need to name my replacement as Commissioner.
我决定任命你
I'm naming you.
你现在才告诉我吗
You mean you're just gonna tell me this now?
辞职以后再告诉我
After you already quit?
如果我之前告诉你  你肯定会拒绝
If I told you before, you'd say no.
-那我就辞不了了  -我还是不同意
- Then I couldn't quit. - Well, I'm still saying no.
-凯斯  -我不是政客
- Kayce-- - I ain't no politician!
你想要政客
You want a politician?
你面前就站着一个
You've got one standing right there.
工棚里还有一个
You got another one in the bunkhouse
-跟孤儿似的  -凯斯
- living like a fucking orphan. - Kayce--
我说了我会帮你经营这里
I told you I would help you run this place,
但我只知道现在这一种方式
and I'm doing that the only way I know how.
我不同意
I won't do it.
我能提个建议吗
Can I make a suggestion?
嗯  只要你愿意接替我
Yeah, as long as it's you.
我不行
Can't be me.
我必须找个家里人去任职  贝丝
I need family in that office, Beth.
那不是还有一个人呢
You can have family in that office.
我不信任他
I can't trust him.
他的所作所为证明了我的看法
All he does is prove it.
他就是这样的人
You can trust him to be exactly what he is.
杰米只会为自己着想  爸
Jamie will always do what is best for himself, Dad.
他会利用这个职位来讨选民的欢心
And he will use the office to become popular with his constituents.
他的选民都是农场主
His constituents are ranchers.
对他们的农场有利  就对我们也有利
What's good for their ranches is good for ours.
快走
Go, go!
快跑  快跑
Run, run, run, run!
快  快  快
Go, go, go!
-我靠  -我操
- Oh, shit. - Goddamn.
这是你第一次套到我
First time you ever got me.
吉米
Jimmy.
好吧  好吧  来吧
Okay, okay, okay, okay, come on.
你现在靠骑烈马为生
You get bucked off shit for a living now.
这对你来说小菜一碟
This'll be a piece of cake for you.
而且考虑到
Take into consideration that
要有脑子才能得脑震荡
you got to have a brain in order to get it concussed,
你肯定没事的
so, you'll be all right.
哥们  别套我的鸡巴啊
Hey, bro, just try not to rope my dick.
不然你妈肯定会很生气
or your mom's gonna be really pissed.
-把绳子给我  -这个我笑了
- Gimme the fucking rope. - That's funny.
开始吧
Okay, here we go.
-好  -开始数
- Okay. - On the clock.
一  二
One, two...
-别往心里去  -三
- It's not personal, it's not personal. - Three!
跳
Jump!
这就是报应  贱人
That's what we call karma, bitch.
报应
Karma.
你妈肯定会很生气
Your mom's gonna be really pissed.
帅哥  到你了
Hey, pretty boy, you're up.
我就算了
Uh, no, I'm good.
算了
You're good?
-是的  -什么
- Yeah. - What?
他不想玩就算了
He don't gotta if he don't want to.
不  杰米  你也得恪尽职守
No, no, Jamie, you gotta pay your dues, bro.
好吧
Yep.
走起  搞起来
Rally, let's rally, let's rally.
-来吧  -怎么玩
- Here we go. - So how does it work?
-对着Y转圈  -对着Y
- Spin on the Y. - Yep, on the Y.
好的
Okay.
这里吗
Here?
好
Okay.
不  这个
No, this.
-这就对了  -我靠
- There he is. - Bro, damn.
对嘛
There he is.
说说你的感受  让我们看看你的感受
Tell us how you feel! Show us how you feel!
好吧  我不太明白为啥要玩这个
Okay, okay, I don't really understand the purpose of this,
但是来吧
but let's do it.
开始吧  数到三  对吧
Let's do it! On three, right?
走起
Take off coming!
我靠
Shit!
你干什么呢
What are you doing?
我想套在他腰上  就不会摔那么重了
I tried to lay it on his waist so he wouldn't go down hard.
你没套上啊
Yeah, well, you sure fucked that up.
他还好吗
Is he all right?
你还好吗
Are you good?
什么时候轮到我套
When is it my turn with the rope?
你们在干什么
What the fuck are you doing?
怎么还没睡
And why are you still awake?
怎么  很晚了吗
What, is it late?
吉米  现在凌晨三点半了
Jimmy, it's 3:30 in the morning.
弄块表  好吗
Get a fucking watch, will you?
-你还好吗  -嗯
- You okay? - Yeah.
小心这些白痴
Be careful with these idiots.
他们没什么脑子
Ain't a brain cell between the bunch of them.
一个小时后就要给整个马厩上鞍了
In one fucking hour you have to saddle the whole barn.
我们明早要配对
We're pushing pairs in the morning.
也就是说到时候要把帐篷搭好
And that means I want wall tents set up
流动炊事车收拾好
and I want that chuck wagon up fucking wind
不然你们就跟灰熊一起睡吧
or you'll be sleeping with the goddamn grizzlies.
你
And you...
你应该管好这些白痴
You're supposed to keep a cap on these morons.
成熟点  好吗  罗伊德
Act your fucking age, would you, Lloyd?
莫妮卡
Monica?
没事吧
Is everything all right?
-嗯  -泰特还好吗
- Yeah. - Tate okay?
凯斯和他在一起
Kayce's with him.
医生给了我们开一些助眠的药  但我
Doctor gave us some pills to help him sleep, but I just...
不相信药  知道吗
Don't trust pills, you know?
是啊  我也是
Yeah. Me either.
总之  我只是
Anyway, I'm just...
我在找上楼的路
I'm trying to find my way upstairs.
我懂  厨房一左转
Yeah, I know... You make a left turn out of that kitchen
就进入迷宫了
and you're in a damn maze.
可不是嘛
Ain't that the truth.
莫妮卡  我一直没机会说声对不起
You know, Monica, I never got to say I'm sorry.
我只是让他去喂个马
I just sent him down there to feed his horse.
想让他担点责任
Trying to give him some responsibility,
虽然这不关我的事  但我应该和你打个招呼的
not that it's my place, but I should've asked.
他被抓走并不是你的错
It's not your fault that they took him.
你能把他带回来  我真是感激不尽
And I can't thank you enough for bringing him back.
这是大家的功劳
Well, we all got him back.
凯斯以前总跟我说保住这个地方
Kayce used to tell me what a war it was for you,
对你来说是一场战争
keeping this place.
150年前  这片土地属于我的人民时
When this land belonged to my people a hundred and fifty years ago,
孩子被偷  男人被杀
children were stolen and men were killed.
家人像牲畜一样被赶了出去
Families herded away like cattle.
什么都没变
And nothing's changed.
但现在印第安人变成你了
Except you're the Indian now.
也许吧
Maybe so.
凯斯说
Um, Kayce said that
你要在牛群附近建营地
you're building a camp near the cattle.
是啊  我也没办法
Yeah. Don't have much choice.
有人想杀牛或者偷牛
Or someone will try to kill or steal them, too.
能帮我个忙吗
Will you do me a favor?
尽管说
Anything.
你能带上泰特吗
Would you take Tate with you?
抬头就能看见星星应该是最有效的药了
I can't think of a better medicine than stars for a ceiling.
你可以帮我吗
Would you do that for me?
当然
Of course.
-晚安  -晚安
- Good night. - Good night.
莫妮卡
Monica?
楼梯在那边
Stairs are back there.
谢谢
Thanks.
好吧  坐副驾啊
All right, coming shotgun there, huh?
把马送回马厩
Stick that horse back in the barn.
把你的装备从工棚拿出来
Move your gear out of the bunkhouse.
拿到哪
Move it where?
屋子里
The lodge.
为什么
Why?
因为我不能让牲畜委员会委员住在工棚
'Cause I can't have the Livestock Commissioner living in the bunkhouse.
我明天会正式任命
I'll make the appointment official tomorrow.
如果你再背叛我
And if you betray me again,
我就当没你这个儿子  明白吗
you are dead to me, son. You understand?
明白  谢谢
Yes, sir. Thank you.
爸
Dad.
我不会背叛你的
I won't betray you.
我保证
You have my word.
迟早会知道你说话算不算话
Well, we're about to find out what that's worth.
凯斯  你和里普领着牧人赶牛
Kayce, you and Rip take the wranglers, start pushing the herd.
我们跟着你们
We'll be right behind.
走吧
All right, let's go.
看好他
Keep an eye on him.
你知道我会的
You know I will.
我
I'm, uh...
委员会的事很抱歉
I'm sorry about the Commission.
但我干不来
It's just not me.
你是我儿子
You're my son.
我很了解你
I know exactly who you are.
永远也不要为此道歉
And don't you ever be sorry for it.
准备好了  老大
We're ready here, boss.
世上没有比这里更美的景色了
Nothing prettier on this earth.
真是太自由了
It's as free as a man can be.
让人不禁怀疑
Makes you wonder...
我们都不在了  谁来养活这个世界
Who's gonna feed this world when there's none of us left.
没有人  罗伊德
Nobody, Lloyd.
这个世界就会挨饿了
This world's just gonna go hungry.
佐罗  佩德罗
Zorro, Pedro...
我回农场了
I'll head back to the ranch.
你们没问题吧
You guys good?
-嗯  -好好享受
- Yeah. - Enjoy.
他们以前就是这样吗  爷爷
This how they used to do it, Grandpa?
没错
Just like this.
你跑过去看看
Why don't you run up there,
能不能最后再捡点柴火
see if you can steal some of the last kindling?
他们有停止命
They have a cease and desist order.
州法院在这里没有管辖权
State court has no authority here.
-让他们滚  -这不是州法院签发的
- Get them out of here. - State court didn't issue it.
海伦纳的巡回法庭
Circuit court out of Helena.
你是雷恩沃特主席的律师吗
Are you council for Chairman Rainwater?
我就是雷恩沃特主席
I am Chairman Rainwater.
埃利斯·斯蒂尔  我的律所代表市场股票
Ellis Steele, my firm is representing Market Equities.
你最好通过法律委员会和我对话
It would be best if you spoke through legal council.
我可以自己来
I'll speak for myself.
没有律师在场或建议
Without council present or advising,
你可以声称自己能力不足
you could claim lack of capacity
法庭可以废除任何提议或暗示的协议
and the court could nullify any agreement suggested or implied.
你是说我听不懂你说话吗
Are you saying I'm incapable of understanding you when you speak?
目前我还不确定
Unclear at the moment.
但我可以向你保证
But I can assure you this:
等我完事了
When I'm done,
我的委托人立场会很明确
my client's position will be perfectly clear.
蒙大拿州立师范学校
美国历史课  教师  莫妮卡·朗
今天上午11点
看看你们
Look at you guys.
我以为在室外上一天课
I thought moving the class outside for a day
能让你们放下手机
would get you off your phones,
但你们还是盯着各自的小屏幕
but you're still staring at your tiny screens.
给素未谋面的人的照片点赞
liking photos of people you've never met
互相评论彼此的生活
and commenting on their lives while they comment on yours.
你们知道你们生活的世界发生了什么吗
Do you have any idea what is happening in the world you live in?
你们觉得屏幕上的照片
Do you think that the photo on your screen
和这个的世界有关联吗
has anything to do with that world?
你们生活的世界正在慢慢缩小
The world you live in is slowly shrinking.
有一小撮男人把你们的世界买了下来
There is a tiny group of men who are buying it
扒光脱尽  向你们贩卖他们提取的东西
and stripping it naked and selling you what they extract.
他们在强暴你们的世界  把夺走的东西再卖给你们
They are raping your world and selling you what they take.
他们贩卖你们喝的水  呼吸的空气
I mean, they sell you the water you drink, the air you breathe
你们却像羊一样排队等着
and you line up for it like sheep.
他们会杀害你们的兄弟  偷走你们的孩子
They will kill your brother and steal your child
污染你们所爱的一切
and pollute everything you love.
你们根本注意不到
And you'll never notice because you're so hypnotized
因为你们被一个不存在的世界催眠了
by a world that doesn't exist.
好吧
Well...
真是浪费我的时间
What a waste of my fucking time.
房子就像船
You know, houses are like boats:
它们需要洗礼
they need to be Christened.
我也这么想过
Well, the thought's crossed my mind.
敬你的新家
To your new house.
谢谢
Thank you.
开玩笑啦
Just kidding.
我再给你倒一杯
Let me pour you another.
不用了  我就要那个  过来  亲爱的
No, no, no, you don't. I'll take that one. Come here, honey.
别担心那只狼  妈妈们
Don't worry about that wolf, mamas.
我不会让它得逞的
I won't let him get to you.
爸爸还没回来
Dad's not back yet.
他回不来
Not coming back.
他今晚要守着牛群
He's with the herd tonight.
他的活算简单的
He got the easy job.
你去哪
Where are you going?
没事的
You're all right.
那只狼  独自在外面游荡
So, that wolf, he's out there walking around by himself,
呼唤它的朋友
calling out to his friends
这样朋友就知道它在哪了
so they always know where he is.
因为他害怕吗
Cause he's scared?
不  狼不会害怕  它们的基因里没有害怕
No. Wolves don't get scared. It's not in their genes.
它们会感到疲倦
They get weary.
也很聪明
They get smart.
就像人一样
Like people.
是啊  像某些人吧
Yeah. Like some people.
我会做噩梦
I have nightmares.
想聊聊吗
Wanna talk about 'em?
嗯
Well...
我在一个房间里
I'm in that room.
地板就这么消失了
The floor just disappears...
我摔下去了
And I fall.
一直下降
Keep falling.
我在尖叫
I scream.
但是没有声音
No sound comes out.
没人听得到  所以没人来救我
No one hears me, so no one comes to help me.
你知道梦是什么吗
Know what dreams are?
梦是你的记忆和想象力
It's your memories and your imagination
混在一碗
all mixed together in... into this soup
半真半假的汤里
of what's real and what's made up.
但这碗汤吧
But the thing about this soup is:
你可以改变配料  泰特
you can change the ingredients, Tate.
你想放什么都行
You can put in whatever you want to.
任何记忆  任何幻想
Any memory, any fantasy.
你可以成为棒球明星
You can... You can be a baseball star
整天拆圣诞礼物
who opens Christmas presents all day long.
这样等你闭上眼睛
So, when you close your eyes later...
就可以定制自己的梦
decide what you're gonna dream.
特定的梦
And that'll be the dream.
你做过噩梦吗
Have you ever had a nightmare?
我做过一个
I have this one...
我在路上开着车
Where I'm driving down the road
有几个人停车了
and there's these people pulled over.
我停车去帮忙  但是
I pull over to help, but...
他们不需要帮助
They don't want help.
他们想要别的东西
They want something else.
他们想要什么
What do they want?
无所谓了
Doesn't matter.
因为你换了配料
'Cause you changed the ingredients.
没错  我换了配料
That's right, I changed the ingredients.
这样就不会成真了
So now it won't come true.
Now it won't come true.